

JOSERIZ M. **CONCEPCION** 

## **PROFILE**

I'm a full-stack (Front-end and Backend) developer for 4 years and Frontend developer for 5 years. I developed applications for business management and analytics and as well as an ecommerce app. I also created mobile app version of some.

## CONTACT

PHONE:

(639) 394006408 (049) 8523-9504

LINKEDIN:

https://www.linkedin.com/in/joserizconcepcion-b74302b4/

EMAIL:

joserizc@gmail.com

PORTFOLIO:

https://jmc-portfolio.netlify.app/#/

# **SKILLS**

- \*Vue (both 2 and 3)
- \*Javascript
- \*Typescript
- \*C#.NET
- \*MS SQL
- \*MS Dynamics CRM

\*HTML

\*CSS3

# **WORK EXPERIENCE**

## Senior Front-end Developer **EMAPTA Philippines Incorporated, Makati City**

September 2023 - present

Development of usable components for front end of a project for customers and in-house portals using Vue 3 and typescript.

## Frontend Developer

## Booth & Partners Philippines Inc - Makati City

November 2021 - September 2023

Working as a front-end developer in a customer portal and support team of an Australian telco company. Continuously test and fix existing bugs and make sure to deploy the desired output within the timeline.

#### **Vue Developer**

### Yondu Inc, BGC Makati City

October 2020 - November 2021

Working as a front-end developer in ecommerce app and content management systems through agile scrum. Creates and implements reusable components for more effective and faster development for the team depending on the requirements of the client.

#### **IT Programmer**

## Fast Services Corporation, Alabang Muntinlupa City

May 2012 - October 2020

Worked closely with software development and testing team members to design and develop robust solutions to meet client requirements for functionality, scalability and performance.

#### Computer Technician

#### Enigma Technologies Inc. Sta. Rosa, Laguna

January 2010 - February 2011

Assembles, configure and troubleshoot computers both laptop and desktop. Network cabling and CCTV installation.

## **EDUCATION**

BACHELOR OF SCIENCE IN COMPUTER ENGINEERING COLEGIO DE SAN JUAN DE LETRAN - CALAMBA 2004 - 2009